<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="32889">
 <title>Firing UP</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>192</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="182">4.5604</rating>
 <info>&#34;Firing Up&#34; is a international collaboration featuring 4 members of &#34;Maniacs of Noise&#34;: Jeroen Tel (NL), Mick Rippon (AU), Thomas Mogensen (DK) and Thomas Egeskov Petersen (DK).

Feel the energy of vintage retro game music combined with the precision of modern production values. A scene-inspired journey of Epic proportions.

==========================

Welcome to Firing Up! A collaborative marathon featuring the musical wares of Jeroen Tel (WAVE), Mick Rippon (MickRip), Thomas Mogensen (DRAX) with a short but very sweet contribution from Thomas Egeskov Petersen (Laxity) - aka: The MANIACS OF NOISE.

It started when Mick said to Jeroen, “let’s write a quick 30 second tune”. So, Mick swiftly tracked a 30 second bassline. Jeroen, being Jeroen, wrote a complimentary melody. Mick, added percussion. Jeroen added more. Mick added more.  Along came DRAX. DRAX added more. Along came Laxity, he added more. The Maniacs of Noise collectively blinked, suddenly the song was 23 minutes. 

The End... actually no, that’s not the end. Firing Up was a result of
1. Many late nights (including last night).
2. Many heated and passionate discussions.
3. Many toxic cigarettes.
4. Many joint listens (yes).
5. Many educational philosophical discussions about nothing.
6. A conception ;) …

For your amusement I will include some technical details about this track.
Song Length: 23 minutes.
Software: Renoise.
Number of unique patterns: 143.
Number of tracks: 29.
Number of Instruments: 56.
Time Spent: 216 days.
Number of Swaps: around 40.

(That was Mick talking). I (Jeroen) would like to add some additional info.
When we started working on this track, we really didn&#39;t have a clue where this would go and when the &#34;tune&#34; started getting really long, keeping track of all the individual instruments (they where allover the place) was a real b*tch! Many hours were spend just to get all those tracks and effects organised. Blips and blops here and there removed and added... a true monster to work with... But as time progressed it became a pleasure to work with it again. I think each of us has heard &#34;Firing Up&#34; many hundreds of times while working on it. The nicest thing about this track is that is has some of all our individual styles and likes combined in one song... Working with talented co-composers is a true inspiration and I hope it shows when you listen to this massively long tune!

Enjoy!</info>
 <songlength>1375</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-26 21:28:41</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-26 21:02:28</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="11">Musicdisk</type>
 <pouetid>56876</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="368">Drax</artist><artist id="655">Laxity [MON]</artist><artist id="792">Mick Rippon</artist><artist id="1935">WAVE</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  <group id="27">Maniacs of Noise</group>
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2011</tag>
  
  <tag>coop</tag>
  
  <tag>hey</tag>
  
  <tag>long</tag>
  
  <tag>megamix</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
  <link>
    <url>http://www.cvgm.net/demovibes/song/11801/</url>
    <comment></comment>
    <type id="16">
        <name>CVGM</name>
        <icon>/static/media/linkicons/favicon.ico</icon>
    </type>
  </link>
 
 </links>
</song>