<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="35103">
 <title>Prisoner</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>0</bitrate>
 <samplerate>0</samplerate>
 <rating votes="48">2.5833</rating>
 <info>--------------------

Tracked by Malekith for the Metal Madness musicdisk, available at
http://www.trackedaggression.com
All guitars and backing vocals were recorded by Malekith in September
2002. Lead vocals were sung by BHS on 29/09/2002.

Originally by Running Wild, available on their &#34;Gates To Purgatory&#34; debut
album (1984) and on the &#34;First Years Of Piracy&#34; collection of
re-recordings (1991). This cover is actually based upon this version,
because it has much more energy than the original (heavier sound, faster
chorus, better backing vocals etc...)

Something quite amusing : read the lyrics, you&#39;ll notice that the words on
RW&#39;s two first albums had nothing to do with their famous pirate-stuff...
Instead, there&#39;s true excellent evil lyrics :) and I think the contrast
with the rock-sounding riffs is quite funny :)

This is certainly one of my favourite Running Wild songs, and has one of
my favorite choruses. It&#39;s just too bad they don&#39;t play it live anymore...
maybe it&#39;s because this song wasn&#39;t written by their mastermind
Rock&#39;n&#39;Rolf, but by their former second guitarist who left a couple of
years later, Preacher ? Singing that chorus at a show must have been truly
amazing, I wish I were one of the old farts who heard that :D


contact me at : lordlg@mangoosta.net
or visit my mod archive : http://malekith.free.fr


Hails to : Cadaver, Tarantula, Hakan, Dragon, Einherjar and everyone else
from the metalscene. Thanks to Friz for organizing the disk !


*------------------------------------------------------------------------*


And finally, the truly intellectual lyrics, so that you can sing along
with the &#34;magnificent choirs&#34; (ahem...) formed by BHS and me (note : the
wimpy voice in the background is mine :D)


Paint in subways, paint in buses
With your Edding big black pentagrams
Black metal graffitis are thrown against the wall

Crucifixes are inversed,
pictures are signed by the triple six
Black metal art is shocking law and order men

(bridge)
Rockers of the underground,
black and heavy is our sound


Lost the money, lost the job
Being catched by the cob
I am living not the role that you wanna give to me

Living life my own way,
not tomorrow, but today
You are against me, but I tell you : K.M.A !

(repeat bridge)

 (chorus)
  We are prisoners of our time,
  but we are still alive
  Fight for the Freedom, Fight for the Right
  We are Running Wild !

*------------------------------------------------------------------------*
</info>
 <songlength>276</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-28 20:28:06</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-14 08:28:15</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 <type id="11">Musicdisk</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="5004">Malekith</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2002</tag>
  
  <tag>cover</tag>
  
  <tag>Guitar</tag>
  
  <tag>GuitarSolo</tag>
  
  <tag>Metal</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>