<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="35105">
 <title>Sacrifice The Rapper</title>
 <status v="B">Banned</status>
 <bitrate>0</bitrate>
 <samplerate>0</samplerate>
 <rating votes="33">2.2121</rating>
 <info>SACRIFICE THE RAPPER


Written, composed and recorded by Malekith in May 2000


For long I had wanted to make a joke-song, and when I got my new ZOOM
GFX-707 guitar effect processor, I thought it would be an excellent
occasion to test it :))
So I found the idea and wrote stupid lyrics during a philosophy class :-)
Then, I composed this bloody shit in one hour, played and recorded it (I
used a microphone plugged into my SB Live 128 soundcard). Finally one of
my friends growled the verses, and I tried to howl the chorus :))

I hope you&#39;ve understood this is not serious at all :)
So have fun with that shit !
Inspiration got from Children Of Bodom and some Cadaver stuff :)

Hails : Cadaver, Dragon, Hakan, HolyBlood, Darkium, Razor, ChristCrusha,
Neomancia, and everyone who likes this :)

hatemail : lordlg@hotmail.com
ICQ : 49731906

Malekith&#39;s homepage : http://listen.to/malekith






LYRICS :

A primate is dancing on a computer beat,
his words are full of hatred, his mind is full of shit.
So boring and stupid, he fills our ears with crap,
annoyed by his insults, we set him a trap.

The rapper is locked up in an unholy cave
with his fellows the rats, he is waiting for a grave !
But time has come to kill, torture and break his bones,
we try to smash his balls but we find out he has none !

 For all your crimes, you&#39;ll have to pay.
 At this point ends your bloody way...

 SACRIFICE THE RAPPER !
 KILL HIM NOW !
 SACRIFICE THE RAPPER !
 LET&#39;S SPILL ALL HIS BLOOD !

With an old rusted blade, the bastard is impaled.
On a big wooden cross, he is finally nailed !
We watch him slowly die, crucified upside down
and tied in a porker&#39;s skin, he is thrown underground !

 The word of violence you spread.
 By your own law you will be dead !

 SACRIFICE THE RAPPER !
 KILL HIM NOW !
 SACRIFICE THE RAPPER !
 LET&#39;S SPILL ALL HIS BLOOD !

</info>
 <songlength>210</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>None</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2013-01-16 05:52:38</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="5004">Malekith</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>