<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="35107">
 <title>Plain Of Bones</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>0</bitrate>
 <samplerate>0</samplerate>
 <rating votes="45">3.6</rating>
 <info>PLAIN OF BONES





Written, arranged and tracked by Malekith
Released on 29/04/99 (my first released original tune)
Redone during December &#39;99 for my new website (in fact, I just checked the
guitar volumes, modified a little bit the drum track and added some
brass and strings...)

This tune was inspired mainly by Edguy and Rhapsody, and also Maiden for
the harmonized guitar solos :)

Thanks to Betrayer for guitar samples and to everyone who helped me.
Hails to Dragon, Hakan, Cadaver, Gnome, and all the Metalscene
members and all those who support metal tracking.
And of course you, if you like this !

Playing time : 6&#39;34

If you prefer the song without the vocal sample, mute the channels 25 and
26


ENJOY THIS !
Malekith : http://listen.to/malekith 
email at : malekith@listen.to
ICQ : 49731906




LYRICS :


As soon as the sun appears in the sky
The battle horns begin to ring around
Our proud soldiers will win or will die
We&#39;re so mighty, they&#39;ll perish without a sound

 We won&#39;t take any prisoners
 No one must survive !

Their peasants have only their forks
Our fierce, dangerous army crushes them down
Kills the young men, expels the folks
We hang their lord on a tree and take his crown

 We slaughtered all of them with rage
 Now all life is gone
 We&#39;ve turned their whole damned village
 Into a plain of bones                      [CHORUS]


We raped and killed, then took their gold
No one remained in the place, a field of corpses
Tired but proud of reaching their goal
The soldiers went back home without remorse

[repeat chorus 2x]

 We&#39;ve turned their whole damned village
 Into a plain of bones...  a plain of bones...

Behind us we leave a plain of bones !
</info>
 <songlength>393</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-16 18:18:12</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-12 02:06:13</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="5004">Malekith</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>