<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="17125">
 <title>Variform (varifoam remix)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="14">3.4286</rating>
 <info>hey dudes, dixan back to scrollerwriting once again, this time in order to entertain your weak brain while you are listening to yet another variform remix (surprise surprise, this is a variform remix collection!). Well, for your pleasure I tried to keep it short and LB managed to give it a proper sound quality, so some of you sick fucks might even like it and might want to play it twice... well, at first I wasn&#39;t really sure if I wanted to take part to this remix idea, since I had the chance to listen to some of the remixes (alkama, LB and frequent, particularly) and well, I thought it wasn&#39;t an easy task! The I started playing some of the loops at half speed and the idea popped out. It also went away quite quickly, that&#39;s why it&#39;s so short... By now you should already be listening to the &#34;rock&#34; part, many props to Amplitube plugin to be able to have any possible sample sounding like a fucked up electric guitar which has been smoking cigarettes since its childhood, I really love it! I&#39;ll soon end up using Amplitube as realtime master filter, so all my playlists will sound very evil... or maybe not... oh fuck, the tune is probably about to end and I still haven&#39;t wrote a line about what you all expect from a scrolltext... the greetings list! so, in random order: everyone in the suomiscene, everyone at playboy mansion, the mighty demomafia, buenzli orgas, the mad portogues cardrivers, the sick dutch fucks, the norwegian inquisition, ze germanz expecially the freaks from hamburg, everybody in drifters, somebody in hungary, a few ones in France, Navis, Nina and that international free soul called Truck... hey, are you still reading? Get away, it&#39;s over, choose a new one!... .. .. .. .. This scroller will now repeat .. .. .. ..</info>
 <songlength>178</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-03 07:18:03</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-04-27 07:04:38</lastplayed>
 
 
 <pouetid>20435</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1650">Dixan</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>