<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="41907">
 <title>Small Matters of the Heart (Party Version)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>228</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="16">3.75</rating>
 <info>[b]Comments from the makers:[/b]

Cryptic:
Finally we are back with a new intro! First one with our new engine. Not a lot of time for proper design this time around since most time has been spent on
coding and bugfixes but at least we got something released. Expect a cleaned up final to follow in the not to distant future when we have recovered from the party deadline crunching.

Velo:
So here we are, once again at Revision getting no sleep. It feels great releasing something new finally,especially in a compo like this, hope you enjoy! Consider this a party version that needs polishing, 
we did not have time to fit all the things we wanted so expect a final version (hopefully not two years from now).

There are some artifacts in the sound that may or may not be noticeable, just pretend its an old vinyl. It will probably, among other things, be fixed in a final version.


----------------------------------------

No room in this party version, but greets fly out to:

Mercury, Conspiracy, Ctrl-Alt-Test, Brain Control, Fairlight, Farbrausch, Censor, #ukscene allstars, EDiS, Tulou, Ate bit, Scullar, Triad,  DCS, Nature, FlowersFX, Outbreak, Cellfish, Razor1911, Traktor, Whazzah, SystemK, The Gang, RGBA, Panda Cube, rtificial</info>
 <songlength>349</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-04-26 18:47:11</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-04-08 03:47:43</lastplayed>
 <platform id="41">64K exe</platform>
 <type id="4">Compo Entry</type>
 <pouetid>65336</pouetid>
 <ytid>foYcHp40HTg</ytid>
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1294">Velo</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  <group id="405">Approximate</group>
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2015</tag>
  
  <tag>Revision</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
  <link>
    <url>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=foYcHp40HTg</url>
    <comment></comment>
    <type id="2">
        <name>YouTube</name>
        <icon>/static/media/linkicons/youtube-icon_.png</icon>
    </type>
  </link>
 
 </links>
</song>