<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="44388">
 <title>Gettin&#39; A&#39;s Just to Show the G&#39;s</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>127</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="12">2.4167</rating>
 <info>&#34;Learning can be a breeze.. Ain&#39;t cool to be a fool!&#34;

From the (never released) album &#34;A Little Nach Music&#34;. Published June 2002.

Download link:
https://web.archive.org/web/20070211052111/http://virt.vgmix.com:80/music/nach/mc_nachbar_-_gettin&#39;_a&#39;s_just_to_show_the_g&#39;s.mp3

Yeah, I know better than anybody else how it be.
Nobody else got the lyrical mastery like me.
Throw my flows down seven days a week.
MC Nach got the power that ya all like to see.
Can&#39;t deny school can be a huge drag:
Classes all day make you feel like jet-lag.
Got [some?] bidness that you gotta take of.
Ain&#39;t no time fo&#39; school that you&#39;re aware of.
Wanna live big, ain&#39;t nothing in the game:
A scholar and a G be one and the same.
Get your nice pad, a job that really pays.
Wanna flip burgers for the rest of yo&#39; days?
Thought so. Now I ain&#39;t your &#39;rents
But I&#39;m finna give it straight &#39;cause they got some common sense
So pay attention, study, tap the fountain:
You&#39;ll develop the intellect to bust mountains.
Every day gotta get learned so you can kick it.
Later on in life, education be the ticket.
Think it&#39;s cool tippin&#39; outta class to do some?
Uh-uh, dumb ain&#39;t chillin&#39;: dumb just dumb.

Learning can be a breeze.
Ain&#39;t cool to be a fool.
Gettin&#39; As just to show the Gs,
We put the cool in school.

I&#39;m serious: ain&#39;t no shame acing classes.
Wanna be separated from all the teeming masses,
To raise up and get out of minimum wage? (Bling!)
Ignorance ain&#39;t nothing but a cage.
Y&#39;all be lovin&#39; on your fellow man.
United Way makes you show that you can.
Look it up: hundred percent of all of your goals.
Good Will G gotta play all the roles.
One to the two to the three ...???
One&#39;s enough ...???... gotta play ...???
Don&#39;t let yourself take the Fs and the Ds.
Report card gotta say A-B-Cs.
E-drop in science like Henderson.
Knowledge is the medicine; gotta get your credits in
for the project, the masterful science project.
Heat should be the focus, and a big object.
I&#39;m a true love dawg so I hate to preach
But you all gotta listen what the teachers teach.
Y&#39;all can&#39;t listen if you&#39;re absent every day
Unless you [really bug him?], then go anyway.

Learning can be a breeze...

Midterms! Aw, snap, I hate those.
Sometimes I think I&#39;d be happy with zeros.
After all, it&#39;s a big round number
But I ain&#39;t happy being smart as a cucumber.
Science, math, history and English...
I can&#39;t think of anything that rhymes with English.
Maybe if y&#39;all paid attention all the time
It wouldn&#39;t be so hard to come up with the rhyme.
Written word, that&#39;s a big thing,
Gotta ...???... good with the writing
&#39;Cause you take it afterwards, and you got it to show
In your P-O-R-T-folio.
Another thing: gotta keep reading every week.
Five books sayin&#39; that your mind&#39;s staying asleep
??? in shape, you gotta keep the books right.
Might be boring, but later it&#39;ll be tight.
The key to knowledge is keepin&#39; it real.
Now that you&#39;ve heard my lyrical appeal
Go forth, prosper, study for your fame,
Help keep your mind at the top of the game.

Learning can be a breeze...
</info>
 <songlength>268</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-05 16:38:23</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-04-18 04:30:31</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="8">Newschool</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1741">MC Nachbar</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Rap</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>