<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="4320">
 <title>Summer Storm</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="10">3.2</rating>
 <info>Hihoooo!

This is


SUMMER STORM

by

MAD GOD


Hey, coming up like a heavy hurricane this tune is going to blow your
minds.

Listening instructions:


Imagine yourself standing on the field with an amazing stormfront
coming up right next to you. You are taken away by it&#39;s power, whirled
around and then you are able to reach the top of the clouds. Gazing at th
e sun you approach the blue sky...

Or something like that. I know I&#39;ve got nothing else to do than writing
you some stuff like that above. But I looked at that message-window and it
was so empty and lonely and... but enough of that.

This tune is the result of the boring Saturday mornings, when I get up,
still curing the coma of the last night and the only thing I&#39;ve got to do
is to abuse my computer for tracking music. After the last two
&#34;orchestra&#34;-XMs, I thought the time has come again to make something
primitive again. So I took my worst and biggest piano-sample, a really
bad
basedrum and a simple beep-sample and here it is, my newest dance-track.
Or whatever you would call that style. Well, finally composing this piece
of music took me about one day hard and less hard work.

I hope you enjoy it and we&#39;ll see what&#39;s next.

I promise: the next one will be an XM again. (less channels and you don&#39;t
have to spend such a lot of time in reading this damn messages.)


That&#39;s it, MAD GOD 01-10-2000
(e-mil: jan.streuffokay.net)

-Ah yes, and don&#39;t believe in things trackers tell you who have words like
&#34;MAD&#34; in their callsigns.

Cya! 

As you can see, I&#39;ve 
not been idle for the 
last few days. 

This is: 

&#34;Summer Storm&#34; 

by MAD GOD 

written 08.01.2000 
released 10.01.2000 


feel free to distribute 
this file... 
...but please don&#39;t touch 
anything!!! 


all samples have been 
converted to 8bit, 
because the original 
size was about 5MB... 
;-) 
</info>
 <songlength>276</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2017-07-08 01:55:59</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2017-06-30 17:45:51</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="712">Mad God</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>