<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="575">
 <title>Logic Air Force (BeaT&#39;s Remix)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="108">3.5556</rating>
 <info>&#34;It all started when I got an email from someone in Japan. This person had heard some of my music and was wondering if I might be willing to arrange a song as part of an Internet-based project called &#34;P-MODEL Global Tribute.&#34; The Japanese techno-pop group P-MODEL was celebrating their 20th anniversary, and they were organizing this project to give fans around the globe (most of which were in Japan, of course) a chance to make their own versions of P-MODEL songs and write their own P-MODEL-inspired music. So I figured I&#39;d give it a shot. I ended up being voted 1st place and having my song included in an issue of the CD-mag &#34;Nikkei NetN@vi&#34; -- very kewl ^__^&#34;

[i]Lyrics:

UNDO time, delete three minutes of the past with the specialized aircraft;
Fly on a course around the sphere that welcomes us in a million different ways.

Hei e, hei e,
One-minute mark and we see the vision;
A crash along the winding route
Deletes the fence around the peaceful phantoms.

Yumeni mita, saisei no sora, saikai no sora.
Ah--

REDO fire, launch and relaunch all the missiles a thousand and one times;
Target the threat, fire upon the shadows that close a million passages.

Kabe e, kabe e,
Two-minute mark and an awful connection;
We dodge the trashy fantasy
And delete the wall and its deviating task.

Yumeni mita, saisei no hie, saikai no hie.
Ah--

[The sky of my dream]
[The land of rebirth]
[The day of reunion]
[P-MODEL OR DIE]

Yumeni mita, saisei no hie, saikai no hie.
Ah--

&#34;CAN DO&#34; brings a bombing raid upon the neuron from three minutes ago;
Burn the flags, the flapping flags that are shutting out a million chances.

Hai e, hai e,
Three minute mark and we see behind us;
A crash deletes the drunken powers;
I see the code reborn with &#34;CAN DO&#34;!

Yumeni mita, saisei no chie, saikai no chie.
Ah--[/i]</info>
 <songlength>260</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-05 11:08:19</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-30 13:42:48</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="5">Remix</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="102">BeaT</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Lyrics</tag>
  
  <tag>Remix</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>