<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="28749">
 <title>Dulcedo Cogitationis (remix)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>192</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="22">3.9091</rating>
 <info>Since the original tune had these really heavy digi-drums, I decided to experiment a bit with these really sharp and &#34;slappy&#34; snares, followed by standard, but higher pitched 909-drumkits, with a very high compression ratio, and adding these little nuskool retrig stuffs.
Not all tune parts are covered, the beginning theme comes back at the end because I didn&#39;t like the rest of the original, so I brought back the beginning patterns with some extra melodies I figured from the rest of the song.

An interesting thing is the game itself. It was prolly the first game I really noticed the music in because the digi-samples sounded so tough and heavy. It was probably the first game where I looked for the name of the composer, and since then I was able to say, &#34;yes, the music is good, it&#39;s Hülsbeck&#34; :-) (The another one was prolly Thing Bounces Back)

The game itself was rather bad if you consider other games in the same genre, it was basically a screen with two wizard-like thingies shooting each other. What really killed the game was a special move, that made the character release a Pac-Man-like chomping thingy which started to pursuit the enemy and it was reasonably faster than the player, so it was only a matter of time before the chomper ate the opponent. This reducted the game to the &#34;who-can-shoot-that-spell-first-and-then-run-away-as-long-as-possible&#34; level, which was a shame because of the great music.</info>
 <songlength>206</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-01 14:29:30</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-28 16:19:25</lastplayed>
 
 <type id="5">Remix</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1390">Gargaj</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>