<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="12042">
 <title>Variform (surface mix)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>320</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="59">4.0508</rating>
 <info>Hello all you happy fuckings-senders, this is Gargaj speaking in this lovely Variform musicdisk, and I&#39;m happy that you got this far in reading, because that means you didnt stop the tune after the first 10 seconds, and also that more importantly, the musicdisk got finally released! As I am already completely clueless about what the scroller should contain, I guess I share some thoughts about the song itself: What I originally intended the style to be was somewhere among the lines of John B or Counter Strike, fast jungle and breakbeats with trancy electro leads. This pretty much went overboard fast since it just didn&#39;t cut it, it lacked character. A week later out of complete accident I turned down the song speed to half and I was amazed how different the whole vibe sounds. It was much easier to build on that kind of beat and tempo and I had a much easier way of building up the characteristics of the original song this way, and also, as evil as I am, add some Imatran Voima samples. (Wait wait wait! Listen to this part, it&#39;s cool!) After some additional tips by my friends (Hi Nina! [:)]  I managed to create something I was finally proud of. ... Is the song still going? Oh well. Greetings go out to PS for some reason and everyone who was at Function 2005. Oh and finally greetings to Lady Manhattan for working on that alternative platform I got her... ... Vazzegmá mikorvanmá vége kiba szkroller. Na majd most... .. .. .. This scroller will now repeat .. .. .. ..</info>
 <songlength>265</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-02 22:27:57</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-31 01:14:35</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="5">Remix</type>
 <pouetid>20435</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1390">Gargaj</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Remix</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>