<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="39086">
 <title>Super RobCo Disco Battle</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>319</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="9">3.6667</rating>
 <info>SoundCloud link:
https://soundcloud.com/dualtrax/dualtrax-artfx-super-robco

---

Pump up the volume!

Super RobCo Disco Battle started as a Sunday afternoon project in mid-June 2013. The idea was to create a classic arcade battle melody spiced up with a techy Disco groove. It took around half a day to compose the basic melodies and two more studio sessions with Artfx! (https://soundcloud.com/artfx) to pimp it up with a jumpy Sega bassline, self-made arcade sound effects, additional Disco percussions &amp; an awesome mastering.

The name of the track is a reference to the computer/console game Fallout &amp; and is especially dedicated to the legendary “RobCo Industries” corporation, one of the biggest &amp; most influential computer and robotics corporations in the (future) United States of America. Just imagine Mr. Handy &amp; Yes Man fighting a deadly “John Travolta style” Disco battle in front of a Nuka Cola vending machine. Makes perfect sense, huh? :)

An early beta version of the track has been released in issue #14 of the weekly Chiptune Podcast “This Week in Chiptune” by DJ Cutman (https://soundcloud.com/djcutman).

Hitboxx ( https://soundcloud.com/hitboxx ), a Chiptune composer from France created a cool breakbeat remix of an earlier version of the track. You can listen to his version here:
https://soundcloud.com/hitboxx/dualtrax-artfx-super-robco?in=dualtrax/sets/super-robco-disco-battle

Super RobCo Disco Battle was created using Renoise (http://www.renoise.com/) &amp; Cubase (http://www.steinberg.net). The lead and some of the bass samples are from the NES &amp; the Sega Mega Drive. The Chiptune arps have  entirely  been designed in Renoise. 
</info>
 <songlength>200</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-05-30 01:18:24</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-11 02:53:18</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="1">Chiptune</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="5647">Artfx!</artist><artist id="2059">Dualtrax</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>