<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="22788">
 <title>Variform (horn-y house cut)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="41">4.2439</rating>
 <info>Hiya. I am usually very lazy in writing anything noteworthy to things like this, so here&#39;s some typical blabber ... I started remixing it in the beginning of 2004. Main point was this : since electro as a style is somewhat quite limited on flow and groove (because of ... well, electro riddims), I plain wanted to make it a bit more dancefloor oriented. This was where it started to take form; cutting and fudging up the basslines on a groovy house background. Next thought was to add some organic hook to bring some flavour on top, so I found out that sexy brass-lines fit into the &#39;chorus&#39;-part and so on. This all worked great until I forgot the &#39;less is more&#39;-rule and stuffed that almost ready version to nearly a level of ear tiring nonsense. Well, not long after I lost all interest in working with it and left it lying into the depths of my harddrive. About a year later (first quarter of 2005) I dug it up from it&#39;s grave and went to visit Doctor Bitchard for some sonic surgery. We reconstructed the song structure a bit and I recorded some additional sounds from his lovely Access Virus-synth, before it was at the point of just minor polishing and mastering, which of course was done by the man himself. That&#39;s about it. It may not be the most interesting remix you come across here, but at least I think it works as it&#39;s supposed to. Remember kids, play it LOUD! ... Oh, and greetings to everyone, especially the nice people in Spain and Finland. You rock, you rule. [:)]  .. .. .. .. This scroller will now repeat .. .. .. ..</info>
 <songlength>302</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-25 00:33:27</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-24 10:06:50</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="5">Remix</type>
 <pouetid>20435</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="3392">Pinza</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2005</tag>
  
  <tag>brass</tag>
  
  <tag>Jazz</tag>
  
  <tag>Remix</tag>
  
  <tag>Untz</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>