<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="19404">
 <title>Variform (sinus)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="17">2.4706</rating>
 <info>okei, its playing. right! first i wanna say that i am drunk again..yes, its my hobby. no..oooh! yes it is. no really it isn&#39;t. or is it? .. some words of this song. i was very drunk when i did it. okei this doesn&#39;t start well does it? i had problems &#39;cos my chair wasnt up to its task at keeping my balance..well, lets not put all this quilt on my chair. its just an object. but so am i..i love to stay high. permanent things get 80s hair cut. yes! but final countdown is the shit. europe, i want to greet everyone in that wonderful band. and kim wilde, ken lazslo, mike mareen, azebo..okeiokei .. forward--&gt; .. so i listen to this song very many times. very many. and..i cant remember, but at morning it sounded ready to me. yes, ready wasn&#39;t the first thing that slipt my mind..it was pussy, i can as well admit it. its was PUSSY. and ass..but mainly PUSSY. i had a headache and my throat was quite sore. im a chainsmoker you know.. sometimes when im with a woman i had to stop smoking. but..ass..well, fuck. not always =D on this point i had to shout out my word for all the pussies out there..and i dont mean you little bitchard;) oo, yes i do..hiihii;) *smack* im in so in need right now..hei, for all the ladys reading this and identifying their man of their dreams. please contact me at jari.pitkanen@gmail.com -- let&#39;s get together. i&#39;m your dog! .. well forward. .. some greetings. .. cruz / enoughrecords, erik / mirakelmusik, jukka-pekka flander, sofi / tangled, all at garage flower, teemu, tommi / anni, mfx, kewlers and for everyone that thinks they know me ..and last but not least for little bitchard for this great opportunity to humiliate myself by typing this shit out! okei se siitä. onnex mutsi ei nää tätä paskaa.. voi vittu, vedä käteen! ... btw. imekää munaa! oikeesti.. .. .. .. .. This scroller will now repeat .. .. .. ..</info>
 <songlength>182</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-27 07:49:29</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-06-13 01:07:23</lastplayed>
 
 <type id="11">Musicdisk</type>
 <pouetid>20435</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1616">1in10</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Experimental</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>