<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="43031">
 <title>Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>195</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="38">3.6579</rating>
 <info>2nd place in the 2016 Streaming Music compo at Revison.

A mostly complete attempt at lyrics:
--------------------------------------
So your day has not been great so far.
No seats left and all your entries are gone but your harddisk crashed.
So you team up for an entry, it&#39;s quite a drunk assembly, that&#39;s what you get for using Commodore.

[So your day sucks? Doesn&#39;t matter. We gonna help you. Uh-huh.]

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky.
What can we say we love 4k C++, and salmiakki.

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky.
What can we say we love 4k C++, and salmiakki.

You can&#39;t concentrate so you walk outside for a drink or three by the fireplace you meet Abductee.
The bonfire gets hotta.
You pass out from vodka.
Where is everyone to get the entry done.

[It don&#39;t matta. We gonna make your day. Uh-uh uh-uh.]

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky. (ohhhh)
What can we say we love 4k C++, and mystic Okkie.

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky. (ohh ohhh oh ohhh)

We&#39;ll fix your file Amiga style (C++), and we got Okkie. (ohh ohhh oh ohhh)

[You don&#39;t need to be dealing with this shit alone. Ain&#39;t nobody got time for dat.]

You said you would rock the compo with your funky crew.
Now your code and shaders are overdue.
The deadline&#39;s coming closer you feel like a poser and you have no clue how to pull it through.

[[It&#39;s always been time to call us but sure as hell it is now.]]

You got your entry finished and entered after all.
Now you wander mindlessly around the hall.
But then there&#39;s an announcement your entry has bounced and Evilbot has replied: YOU&#39;RE DISQUALIFIED.

[[Oh come on now you have to call us right?]]

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky. (Lucky, lucky, lucky)

[Ain&#39;t nobody got time for dat.]

What can we say we love 4k C++, and salmiakki. (yakki, yakki)

Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE, in between, and you&#39;ll get lucky.
We are you muses. (muses, muses)

Itsy bitsy teeny weeny ddt in a minikini.
We&#39;ve heard, enough excuses.

[You don&#39;t need to be dealing with this shit alone. We&#39;re in this together.]

(Ahhhhh, ahhhhh)

[We&#39;re in this together.]

[[Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE]]

[[Call 1-800-DEMOSCENE]]

[[[We&#39;re sorry the number you have dialed is not in service. Please check the number and try again]]]</info>
 <songlength>235</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-14 06:00:23</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-06-08 09:47:50</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="4">Compo Entry</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="569">jco</artist><artist id="849">Netpoet</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2016</tag>
  
  <tag>coop</tag>
  
  <tag>Revision</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
  <link>
    <url>https://demozoo.org/music/155116/</url>
    <comment></comment>
    <type id="23">
        <name>Demozoo</name>
        <icon>/static/media/linkicons/demozoo-16x16_RJXlval.png</icon>
    </type>
  </link>
 
 </links>
</song>