<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="33308">
 <title>You Can&#39;t Handle the Commodore</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>256</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="35">2.1429</rating>
 <info>Tied for 7th place in the music compo at Blockparty &#39;09

Download: http://www.robohara.com/?p=1424

Lyrics
---
[First Verse]

Listen up kid, it’s time to put down the Wiimote
Drop the 32-bits, hop into my boat
Talkin’ trash like a punk emcee,
I’ll punch you in the face like the Ninja from Bruce Lee!

My kid is the son of an 8 bit,
In front of a sixty-four’s where I sit.
I like to battle, but I won’t bark on,
I’ll toast your ass like the Phoenix from Archon.

I’m great at a million games man,
When you were in diapers, I was cleanin up Wasteland.
Summer Games, Winter Games, World Games, too,
California Games cured my summertime Blues

Wanna play? Bring a DB9 Stick,
I got an old Epyx that I’ll kick your ass with.
You want mercy? Well you better start wishin,
You beatin’ me’s an Impossible Mission.

Like HERO, I’m about to fly,
With a disk notcher I’ll use your backside,
Like Load Runner you’ll drop your load,
Then I’ll pick up your package of gold.

You’re a headbanger, cuz you bang your drive’s head
You’re like a zombie, and you’re already dead,
And I’m a serial killer with a serial cable,
Cuz you’re retarded, or should I say disabled?

Let’s play Pitfall, you know what to do?
Well take notes chump and I’ll give you a clue.
Jump over the logs, then swing on the vines,
And then you gotta UH OH out of time!

This battle’s over, I’ve already won,
Cuz you come last like comma eight comma one.
Feelin’ lucky? Wanna test your ability?
You beatin’ me? Realm of Impossibility.

[Chorus]

I’m the king of [the Commodore]
You don’t want none of [the Commodore]
You can’t handle [the Commodore]

[Second Verse]

So bring what you got, whatchu think, you’re bad man?
Well I got skills yo, but I ain’t Rad Man
Cuz he does art, yo and I play games, yo
so pick up a stick and I’ll bring the pain, yo

Cuz here is the church and here is the steeple,
your only friends are Little Computer People
In Skate or Die you always fall,
So you can suck on my Wizballs

I’ll cut your head off, like Barbarian
I’m bout to school you like a librarian
Your expectations are never gonna be met
I’ll rip you apart like Racing Destruction Set

You think your bad, you better get your facts on,
Cuz I can rock a perfect score in Zaxxon,
Wanna play some Hacker or Hacker II,
Well look it up bitch I wrote the walk thru.

Your face is red, I can tell your pissed,
Cuz I whipped you in the Way of the Exploding Fist
Cuz I kick ass, and I never come in last,
And I’ll beat your ass at Boulderdash

Player one, player two, it just don’t matter,
In Karate Champ your face will splatter,
I’ll whip you, like a goddess wearing leather
You can Stay a while, but don’t stay forever.

In Beach Head you took two the dome,
You gonna need a Space Taxi to get you home.
Yes I’m better than you, you’re not just paranoid,
and I’m a 999 in Paradroid

Three minutes and this track is through
I’m number one and you’re 6502
We’re done here, and there’s the door,
I was right, you can’t handle the Commodore.

[Chorus]

[Closing Comments]

That’s right, he’s the king.
You better run/stop your mouth.
Aw your disk is all floppy …
He’s got two kids — Vic, and Sid.
He’s gonna get you with an Isepic.
Yeah, you can’t handle the Commodore …</info>
 <songlength>180</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-28 09:32:41</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-06-09 03:27:48</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="4">Compo Entry</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="4798">Flack</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2009</tag>
  
  <tag>Blockparty</tag>
  
  <tag>C64</tag>
  
  <tag>Lyrics</tag>
  
  <tag>modem</tag>
  
  <tag>Rap</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>