<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="30246">
 <title>That&#39;s the Shit</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>185</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="80">2.6</rating>
 <info>Winner of the music compo at Main 2010.

LYRICS

Hello boys&#39;n&#39;girls. I&#39;m here tonight to clean up after all the ooftza ooftza music. This song is about hip swinging and hand 
waving, and just so that everybody out there understands, I&#39;m gonna do this in many languages. Watch out for yours. 
Just get your hands up and your hips movin&#39;, and we&#39;re good to go. 

Let&#39;s go, baby, that&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit!
Gyerünk, bébi, ez a fasza, ez a fasza, ez a fasza!
Allez, bébé, c&#39;est de la merde, de la merde, de la merde.
Ven, cariño, ven cari, esta bien.

Habt ihr Bock?!? Dann zeigt uns&#39;n paar Hände!
Habt ihr Bock?!? Dann zeigt uns eure Hände!

But if that&#39;s not your thing, just go over 
and get a drink with the ladies at the bar.
They go, &#34;Ooh, vous êtes un coder? C&#39;est magnifique!&#34;
And your knees get weak, you can hardly speak.
Then go to your laptop,  act like Chewbacca,
and fix your entries for real real good.
This way or that, please come back
Cuz then it&#39;s on, cuz then it&#39;s on!
Cut then we get crazy down there, we get crazy up here.
We get totally crazy, it&#39;s just craazzeeEEEEEee!
So here we go!

Let&#39;s go, baby, that&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit!
Gyerünk, bébi, ez a fasza, ez a fasza, ez a fasza!
Allez, bébé, c&#39;est de la merde, de la merde, de la merde.
Ven, cariño, ven cari, esta bien, esta bien.

Habt ihr Bock?!? Dann zeigt uns&#39;n paar Hände!

So, jetzt lassen wir unseren Special-Freund, den Ecki Ubumbu 
aus Hessisch Uganga, mal ein Bass-Solo machen.

Gut. So, das hätten wir. Jetzt legen wir alle noch mal schön den 
Döner weg und nehmen die Hände hoch. Ich will jetzt wirklich alle 
Hände sehen, auch deine, DocD. All your hands!

Let&#39;s go, baby, that&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit! That&#39;s the shit!
Helft alle mit, dass hier endlich was geht, endlich was geht, endlich was geht!
Gyerünk, bébi, ez a fasza, ez a fasza, ez a fasza!
Hände in die Lüfte und heiß gedreht, heiß gedreht, heiß gedreht.
(Repetition)

Bo&#39;i motek, ze gadol.
Min na o ide odorou.

Oh, vous êtes un coder, c&#39;est magnifique!

Thank you, and good night.</info>
 <songlength>182</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-04-19 18:48:38</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-03-07 13:41:29</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="4">Compo Entry</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="849">Netpoet</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  <group id="317">Park Studios</group>
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>2010</tag>
  
  <tag>anal</tag>
  
  <tag>Compowinner</tag>
  
  <tag>Lyrics</tag>
  
  <tag>MAiN</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>