<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="10801">
 <title>Mendelian Miscarriage</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>192</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="18">2.5556</rating>
 <info>(c) 1996 Chuck Biscuits / kosmic

oi!
lookie here!
cb babble.mode.on

welp, here&#39;s a bit of trance for those of you into the deep german tip.  hope it gets some butts movin at your place - this should be reproduced in sparkling studio quality soon and pressed onto sexy little slabs of black vinyl (dj&#39;ing being the art of the future, of course :)

and remember - syncopation increases your funkiness factor :)

wow kids,i did something NEW and that i&#39;ve NEVER DONE BEFORE in this track

for those interested in any other work i&#39;m doing, i know i&#39;ve been quite quiet release wise lately, that&#39;s because there&#39;s been alot of un-musical stuff going on which i&#39;ve had to deal with and also because i&#39;ve been tracking and not releasing; like the naughty devil i long to be.

nevertheless, there might be a few more of these little ditties coming your way from my brain soon, including (yet more) deep trance and some other styles i&#39;ve yet to encroach upon (up till now, err, then)..

big chemical hellos to Ozone for the DAT work; much appreciated and the tape has served its purpose and others which i would never have dreamed of; big big thanks :)

make sure you stop in at the -REAL MUSIC- section of your local record outlet today!

respects to: kazu kimura, vivid (more co-ops yes definately :), basehead, injekted (phatness trackerised), sybaris (superb work), subhuman (goa demon :), and anyone who goes out for the music and not just the fringe benefits &lt;smile&gt;.

tap! tap! &lt;clink&gt; wake up &lt;tap&gt;

argh insurance company collection demons chasing after me! no! save me from the mercantile assailant! arrrgh!

i always expected the bad guys would be coloured red or green or something - instead they&#39;re just like me, only with expensive mobile phones</info>
 <songlength>487</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-12 13:43:24</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-26 20:26:32</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 <type id="3">Oldskool</type>
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1843">Chuck Biscuits</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>long</tag>
  
  <tag>Techno</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>