<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="28509">
 <title>Variform (Wonder remix)</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>192</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="35">3.6</rating>
 <info>Hi! Wonder on the keyboard! This is my remix for one of the most uplifting demosongs ever. As I&#39;m not very related to remixes stuff, I just tried to bring the song to a closer music style in which I could be more comfortable. So I plugged my guitar and started to experiment. I tried to imitate almost every sound they (Mel &amp; lb) made with synths using only my guitar (a Parker P-38 with DiMarzio pick-ups) and my effects processor (a Vox Tonelab). And this is the final result. I didn&#39;t want the song to become a heavy metal song, I just tried to keep the original feeling but giving the song the human touch that synths cannot achieve, so there are some of the original samples in the final mix, but from the beginning till the end there&#39;s always a guitar to be listened to.. .. And now some thanks and greets. First of all a very special thank you to Little Bitchard and the Kewlers people for thinking of me for this project, it&#39;s a honour :). Also thanks to Leia for her special patience in contacting and informing me about the project. Super-greetings to all the others involved in the project (Hi!) and to Tekno, Ithaqua, Naif, Reboot, Recena and Sml for forcing me to get out of Spain to latest BP :D.. Usual-greetings to all my usual demoscene friends (you know who you are, and you know that your are many and I&#39;m very lazy). Byeee! .. .. .. .. This scroller will now repeat .. .. .. ..</info>
 <songlength>304</songlength>
 <locked>False</locked>
 <locked_until>2017-10-19 11:56:24</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2017-10-12 22:47:21</lastplayed>
 <platform id="1">Other</platform>
 <type id="11">Musicdisk</type>
 <pouetid>20435</pouetid>
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="1590">Wonder</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Guitar</tag>
  
  <tag>Remix</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>