<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="16392">
 <title>Viens au soleil</title>
 <status v="B">Banned</status>
 <bitrate>128</bitrate>
 <samplerate>44100</samplerate>
 <rating votes="54">1.6296</rating>
 <info>What an adventure for the young musician i was ! Remember, few month ago, i was flushed by Boys Band concept as 2 be 3 and The Backstreet Boys.. I was also imagining surfing on this concept… Quickly i imagined as tiny story with young teenager trying to catch girls with their cars  and muscles… the S.S.S. was borned with Cyborg Jeff (Pierre Martin) and Tbob (Valentin Boigelot). Musicaly it was most inspirated from DJ Sash, and the lyrics had something from a not well known old dance songs called : Sortez Couvert.

The project should not go further, as a lot of other one, but my friend Valentin was so enjoyed by this, he let it grow up… The father and brother of Wivine Rombauts, who was in the same theatre troupe of us had just finishing a home recording studio. Waooouw !

Didier was the sound engineer and this father André was more focused on video aspect. The project was settle, we’ll record the track and then we’ll work on a movieclip realised on Quéna Arèdje !

This new meeting with Didier Rombauts still be reserved, hidden behind his mixing table, no one could imagine how friend we will be later ! I was just a client, and he was the engineer. The song was quickly recorded… The soundtracker format didn’t let us mix it easely with the Fostex, i easely recorded my voice, and we took more time with Val, who was young singer at that time !

Movieclip realisation was realy fun, We didn’t search something serious, so we shooted not so far the studio in field and children amusement places.

Few weeks later, Didier and I discovered we will go to Louvain La Neuve in the same school,… a brand new friendship will started !

Project : Summer Island
Project Download : http://www.jamendo.com/fr/album/9629</info>
 <songlength>204</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>None</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2015-07-03 09:54:16</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 <ytid>AsEEmJPVd2M</ytid>
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="260">Cyborg Jeff</artist><artist id="3702">Tbob</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>coop</tag>
  
  <tag>Eurodance</tag>
  
  <tag>FrenchSpeak</tag>
  
  <tag>OddStuffFromOldNecta</tag>
  
  <tag>OutOfTune</tag>
  
  <tag>summer</tag>
  
  <tag>video</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>