<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="41984">
 <title>Frozen Tears</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>0</bitrate>
 <samplerate>0</samplerate>
 <rating votes="8">3.75</rating>
 <info>v1.0: 2/10/99

FREEZING TEARS

==============
Preliminary Version: Title melody for Tarmalon (IsoRP)

(or whatever)




Dedicated to my sister Anya




Greetings:

Zottel, Burnie, Max, WW, Aramis, Kai
and everybody in our action radius.

Some samples are still ripped. Credits go to:

Warder, Skaven, Zirconia, Purple Motion, Jase and others (couldn&#39;t find
any aliases or names)


Further greetings to: MagicMan, Tina, WGPeople, Awesome



Scenery:

A barbarian raiding party sets foot on a snow covered island which is only
inhabited by woodsmen and farmers. They attack the town.
It is an uneven battle, the townsmen are no match for the savage
attackers. Even the town&#39;s priest is no threat for them, and he is
defeated soon.
A dark figure walks calmly through the town while the battle is still
raging.
He reaches for the priest&#39;s chest and takes an amulet from the dying
body. Then he orders his horde to burn the town and to return to the
ships.
The blazing fire lights up the sky even more than the dawning sun.

Up on the hill, a young woodcutter cannot believe what he is seeing. The
bodies of his people are scattered on the ground. The snow is inked in
red, and the pirates&#39; ships are still visible hear the horizon.

The town was not rich, so their bounty must have been small. &#34;Why would
they have attacked?&#34;, he asks the wind.

It takes him days to bury the dead. Since there are no more hunters
patrolling the woods, wolves already dare to come nearer over the edge of
the hills...

Soon, the lonely woodcutter manages to repair a boat and ventures a sea
journey.
He hopes to reach the continent, to find out more about the barbarian
horde and what they had come for if it wasn&#39;t for gold...</info>
 <songlength>260</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-06-27 06:58:38</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-05-23 01:19:03</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="2776">Gargoyle</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>