<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<song id="41985">
 <title>Echo</title>
 <status v="A">Active</status>
 <bitrate>0</bitrate>
 <samplerate>0</samplerate>
 <rating votes="16">2.125</rating>
 <info>
E C H O

-------



Final version
6th of November 2001

by Gargoyle 2000/2001

a funky brains release



i hear an echo i hear the sound rebound slice thru the silence fill the
air and shake the ground the lake of life is frozen aint safe to cross the
ice never reach the horizon slip and fall never to rise again try to
invoke your fate try to ponder on mystery no heaven&#39;s gate no destination
but destiny . . . 

just like an echo just like a dog around your feet bad luck keeps coming
keeps your track on every street i tried to fool it turns out the fool is
me a thousand voices laughing reverberating endlessly








Respect to Malekith &amp; Cadaver for having tracked &#34;Holy Forest&#34;, which has
become Track of the Year 2000 on modplug.com
This song is also the source for those superb guitar samples. I just
couldnt resist to get my hands on them.
Be sure to get &#34;Holy Forest&#34; by Malekith &amp; Cadaver.



Sample Credits:
Malekith, Narfy, Moby, Purple Motion, and Christoph Zieger.



Thanks to Robert Neussendorfer of the band Gegenstrom for lending me his
microphone; I hope we can get our songs done some evening.



Greetings to all my friends, the ModArchive crew and visitors, the
#modarchive channel roamers on DALnet, and all those magnificent people
who keep the scene alive and kicking.






Hope you like this tune even though my voice is not that blessed with the
ability to sing. :-P



  - Gargoyle / funky brains

	gargoyle@tunestore.de
	www.tunestore.de</info>
 <songlength>312</songlength>
 <locked>True</locked>
 <locked_until>2018-07-31 12:37:15</locked_until>
 <lastplayed>2018-06-11 23:08:45</lastplayed>
 <platform id="8">IT</platform>
 
 
 
 
 
 <artists>
  <artist id="2776">Gargoyle</artist>
 </artists>
 <groups>
  <group id="392">F4CG</group>
 </groups>
 
 <tags>
  <tag>Lyrics</tag>
  
  <tag>Vocals</tag>
  
 </tags>
 <links>
 
 </links>
</song>